(Amy:)intelligent dog uprising.
(Amy:)FYI, we plan on selling out
the human race hard.
(Penny:)In 20 years, who knows
what'll happen with any of us?
(Stuart:)I think you and Leonard
will be together.
(Penny:)-You do?
-Yeah.
(Stuart:)I think you're
the best couple I know.
(Penny:)That's so sweet.
(Bernadette:)-What the hell?
-Excuse me?
Duh, duh, duh...
Let the dead man talk.
(Penny:)So, why do you think that?
(Stuart:)Well, I feel like you guys
make each other better.
(Stuart:)Penny brought Leonard
out of his shell.
(Stuart:)And it seems like Leonard makes Penny
think more deeply about the world.
(Stuart:)I don't know. Together, you two
kind of make one awesome person.
(Penny:)Aw, Stuart.
(Penny:)Now I feel bad for murdering you.
Oh, come on!
Penny did it! I win!
Suck it, jackasses!